

CONTACT



+91 9636447793



savanyadav377@gmail.com



Vill. Bhojayara Th. Chaksu Dist. Jaipur (Raj) Rajasthan - 303903

SKILLS

- PHOTOSHOP
- FIGMA
- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- BOOTSTRAP
- JQUERY
- RESPONSIVE DESIGN
- VISUAL STUDIO CODE
- DESIGN THINKING

EDUCATION

MASTER OF ARTS
 University of Rajasthan Jaipur
 2021-2022

HOBBY

- VOLLEYBALL
- FARMING

SAWAN KUMAR YADAV

— WEB DESIGNER

ABOUT ME

A professional web designer with 14 Month experience in website design. Strong creative and analytical skills. I can build valuable user interface and user experience for clients using my new skills and experience in web design. I want to create engaging, highly interactive web design for the future of the web.

EXPERIENCE

Gitsquare

Nov 2022 - May 2023

 Editing & Design with designing team in the company to build perfect web designs.
 Checking for errors and de-bugging websites.

DVG Soft

Jun 2023 - Present

 Modifying and making changes according to client's requirements.
 Making the website responsive.

PROJECT

- https://gitsquare.com/hotel/index.html
- https://infogear.co.tz/
- https://gitsquare.com/traking-services/
- https://www.advanceorthosolutions.com/
- https://gitsquare.com/dregon-casino-spin/
- https://gitsquare.com/christmas-vibe/
- https://www.gitsquare.com/
- https://gitsquare.com/dregon-spin/
- https://gitsquare.com/mi-orange/
- https://gitsquare.com/jeckpot-spin/
- https://gitsquare.com/ups/